Marjorie Ann Scott papers, 1979-2023.
Congregational Library & Archives
Marjorie Ann Scott papers, 1979-2023.
MS5483
Congregational Library & Archives
0.18 Cubic Feet
(1 box)
Marjorie Ann Scott was born in Bedford, Virginia, on December 1st, 1947. In 1989, Marjorie would become an ordained minister of the United Church of Christ for the Church of the Covenant in Boston. Marjorie would pass away at the age of 61 on January 28th, 2009. This collection contains material from the life of Marjorie Ann Scott and includes autobiographical writing, poems, sermons, letters, remembrances, and more.
Gerlach, Barbara
Scott, Marjorie Ann (1947-2009)
Perry, Faith
Restrictions on Access
Access to this collection is unrestricted and open to the public except for Folder 3, "Recollections of Faith Perry", which is restricted through May 2050.
Acquisition Information
Materials were donated to the Congregational Library & Archives by Barbara Gerlach in September 2023; 2023-48.
Biographical Note
Marjorie Ann Scott was born in Bedford, Virginia, on December 1st, 1947. She would go on to graduate from Westhampton College of the University of Richmond, Duke University, and the Andover Newton Theological Seminary. In 1989, Marjorie would become an ordained minister of the United Church of Christ for the Church of the Covenant in Boston. Others places where she would work include the Boston City Mission Society, Elizabeth Stone House, Assistant Pastor at Grace Church Federated in East Boston, and as an Associate Pastor at the North Prospect Church in Medford. Marjorie would pass away at the age of 61 on January 28th, 2009.
Scope and Contents
This collection contains material from the life of Marjorie Ann Scott and includes autobiographical writing, poems, sermons, letters, remembrances, and more.
Sermons.; Autobiography.; Poetry.; Letters.; Church newsletters.; Gerlach, Barbara
- Obituary and service of worship, undated (Box 1, Folder 1)
- Resume, undated (Box 1, Folder 2)
- Recollections by Faith Perry, 2023 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  Restrictions on Access
  This folder is restricted and cannot be accessed until May 2050.
- Commencement Address, 1979 (Box 1, Folder 4)
- Reflections, March 15, 2000 (Box 1, Folder 5)
- Vision: Healing and Hope, undated (Box 1, Folder 6)
- North Prospect Church newsletter, undated (Box 1, Folder 7)
- A Christmas Story, undated (Box 1, Folder 8)
- And Grace Will Lead Us Home, 1996 (Box 1, Folder 9)
- Letters, undated (Box 1, Folder 10)
- Arise, Shine for Your Light Has Come, undated (Box 1, Folder 11)
- The Sacred, the Demonic, and Imagination, undated (Box 1, Folder 12)
- Sermons, undated (Box 1, Folder 13)
- Poems, undated (Box 1, Folder 14)
- Remembrance by Barbara Gerlach, August 21, 2023 (Box 1, Folder 15)